[{"answer": " OK. Heres our room, Number 524", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Lets go in and check it out", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 13, "question": " OK. Heres our room, Number 524", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Here it is", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Lets go in and check it out", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Steve, this room only has one tiny twin bed.  We cant sleep on that", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Here it is", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Look at the bathroom.  There is only one towel and the tub is full of brown water", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Steve, this room only has one tiny twin bed.  We cant sleep on that", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Eww!  This room is so dirty", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Look at the bathroom.  There is only one towel and the tub is full of brown water", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " We cant stay here", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Eww!  This room is so dirty", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " What should we do", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 19, "question": " We cant stay here", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " I guess we should go complain to the front desk staff", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 20, "question": " What should we do", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Should we", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 21, "question": " I guess we should go complain to the front desk staff", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " We have to.  Were not paying $100 a night for this", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Should we", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " OK, Ill go with you", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 26, "question": " We have to.  Were not paying $100 a night for this", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": "Hello, sir.  Can I help you", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 30, "question": " OK, Ill go with you", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Yes, hi.  We just checked into room 524 and its unacceptable.  We cant sta", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Hello, sir.  Can I help you", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Is there something wrong with the accommodations sir", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Yes, hi.  We just checked into room 524 and its unacceptable.  We cant sta", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Yes, there is.  We booked a room with a king size bed and the room you gav", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Is there something wrong with the accommodations sir", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Im very sorry, sir.  Let me check our computer here to see what happened", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Yes, there is.  We booked a room with a king size bed and the room you gav", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Well, I reserved a king bed.  Two of us cant sleep on a twin", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Im very sorry, sir.  Let me check our computer here to see what happened", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Im very sorry about the mix-up sir.  Would you like us to bring a cot int", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Well, I reserved a king bed.  Two of us cant sleep on a twin", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " OK.  Thank you", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Im very sorry about the mix-up sir.  Would you like us to bring a cot int", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " No.  The room is filthy.    Wed like to be put in another clean room with a kin", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 56, "question": " OK.  Thank you", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " OK.  Let me just see what we have open for the evening.  Unfortunately, i", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 58, "question": " No.  The room is filthy.    Wed like to be put in another clean room with a kin", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Is that the only option", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 62, "question": " OK.  Let me just see what we have open for the evening.  Unfortunately, i", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Yes.  Either that or stay in room 524", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Is that the only option", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " No, we cant do that.  I guess well move to the room with two twins.  Will I get ", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Yes.  Either that or stay in room 524", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Im afraid we cant give you a refund.  We are very sorry for all of thi", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 68, "question": " No, we cant do that.  I guess well move to the room with two twins.  Will I get ", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " So heres your new key.  Your new room is room 358", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Im afraid we cant give you a refund.  We are very sorry for all of thi", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " All right", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 74, "question": " So heres your new key.  Your new room is room 358", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Please let me know if there is anything wrong with that room.  It wa", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 75, "question": " All right", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Thanks", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Please let me know if there is anything wrong with that room.  It wa", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " If theres anything else we can do to make your stay more comfortable", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Thanks", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " OK.  Bye", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 84, "question": " If theres anything else we can do to make your stay more comfortable", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " What a mess", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 88, "question": " OK.  Bye", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " I know.  If this other room isnt clean, then well just go stay somewhere else", "docId": "09-04", "aSentId": 89, "question": " What a mess", "qSentId": 88}]
